Shailesh Patil

Navi Mumbai, Maharashtra patilshaileshr9_t2e@indeedemail.com +91-9967762838

Software Engineer with 10+ Years of experience in developing and optimizing Cloud and Web based software applications. Adapt at implementing new methodologies to determine project performance in different environment to achieve significant project scope and budget improvement.

Work Experience

Senior Software Engineer

Birlasoft Limited July 2016 to Present

Software Engineer

Paramatrix Technologies Pvt. Ltd January 2013 to June 2016

Software Developer

Softlink Global Pvt. Ltd November 2009 to January 2013

Education

B. E. in music & travelling

MGM's College of Engineering & Technology, Kamothe, Navi Mumbai, Mumbai University - Mumbai, Maharashtra

Skills / IT Skills

- Technologies: ASP.NET (MVC and Web Forms), C#, Entity Framework, Web API, WCF
- UI Framework / Scripting Language: Angular, JavaScript, JQuery
- Database: MS SQL Server 2012, 2014
- Cloud Computing Platform: Azure PAAS